Atomic Veterans Records MS005
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject files and reports, 1940 -- 2012; MS005.001; 8.6 Linear Feet
  - Advisory Committee on Human Radiation Experiments: Misc. newsletters and material, 1994 -- 2004; MS005.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Advisory Committee on Human Radiation Experiments: preliminary drafts, 1994; MS005.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Advocacy Committee for Experimentation Survivors - Mind Control, 1997; MS005.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
    This folder contains the text of a videoletter requesting for a presidential hearing on mind control experiments on human subjects.
  - Advocates for radiations veterans and victims, articles and correspondence, 1984 -- 1997; MS005.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Alaska - Human radiation experiments, 1967 -- 1991; MS005.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Alexander, Dr. Leo - Partial index to papers at BU and Duke, 1972; MS005.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Atomic veterans: Assorted original newspaper articles and copies of pertinent stories, 1955 -- 2001; MS005.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Atomic veterans: Misc. newsletters, 1976 -- 2000; MS005.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
    This folder contains issues of publications related to atomic veterans, including Mother Jones, VFW, and DAV.
  - Atomic Veterans Radiation News (AVRRI), 1997 -- 2001; MS005.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Atomic workers and compensation, 1965; MS005.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
    This folder contains two Department of Labor, Atomic Energy Commission publications, "Studies in Workmen's Compensation and Radiation Injury, volume II: The incidence, nature and adjudication of workmen's compensation claims involving radiation exposure and delayed injury," and "Studies in Workmen's Compensation and Radiation Injury, volume III: A report on Ionizing Radiation Record Keeping."
  - Beck, Dr. James: files, Japan, 1947 -- 1975; MS005.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Beck, Dr. James: medical materials on early effects of the atomic bomb at Nagasaki and Hiroshima, 1945 -- 1946; MS005.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Beck, Dr. James: Clinical and Pathological Observations on the effects of atomic bombs, 1945 -- 1946; MS005.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Beck, Mrs. James: correspondence and copies of Dr. Beck's reports, 1982 -- 1985; MS005.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Bibeau, Harold: Oregon prison radiation experiments, 1994 -- 1998; MS005.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
    This folder contains correspondence, proposals, reference materials and reports.
  - Can We Survive a Nuclear War?, 1983; MS005.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
    This is a reprint of a series of articles by Ray Cromley.
  - Certificates of participation and publicity materials, 1945 -- 1984; MS005.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
    This folder contains certificates of participation from atomic bomb tests in Nevada and the Marshall Islands, as well as political cartoons, and publicity for films and events.
  - Congress: correspondence, 1977 -- 1984; MS005.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Congress: correspondence, 1985 -- 1988; MS005.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
    This folder also contains Sandra Marlow's correspondence with the Senate and the Defense Nuclear Agency.
  - Congress: correspondence and reference inquiries, 1990 -- 1994; MS005.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
    This folder also contains Sandra Marlow's correspondence with the Defense Logistics Agency and the National Archives and Records Administration.
  - Congress: correspondence, 1997 -- 2002; MS005.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
    This folder also contains Sandra Marlow's correspondence with the Senate and the Department of the Navy.
  - Congressional Bills, 1985 -- 1989; MS005.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Congressional Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce report: The Forgotten Guinea Pigs, 1980; MS005.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
    This folder contains, "The forgotten guinea pigs: A report on health effects of low-level radiation sustained as a result of the nuclear weapons testing program conducted by the United States Government."
  - Coverups: newspaper articles, 1979 -- 2000; MS005.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Coverups: secrecy of information on effects of radiation, 1985 -- 1998; MS005.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Cummings and Brown: Lawyers (NARS, NAAV, Task Force on Human Radiation Experiments), 1981 -- 1998; MS005.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Department of Commerce: Radiation handbooks, 1951 -- 1954; MS005.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
    This folder contains the DoC Handbook 48, "Control and Removal of Radioactive Contamination in Laboratories," and Handbook 54, "Protection Against Radiations from Radium, Cobalt-60, and Cesium-137.
  - Department of Defense / Office of Civil Defense- In Time of Emergency: A citizen's handbook on nuclear attacks and natural disasters, 1968; MS005.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Department of Energy - Answers to your questions about high-level nuclear waste isolation, 1982; MS005.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Department of Justice - The evolution of scientific understanding of the occupational Hazards of ionizing radiation, 1988; MS005.001.005.00035; Harris, Ruth R.; Hewlett, Richard G. (Box 5)
  - DNA fact sheets, 1980 -- 1989; MS005.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
    Defense Nuclear Agency (DNA).
  - DNA: Visual Information Division - film listing, 1972; MS005.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Electromagnetic modern technology and mind control research, 1986 -- 2000; MS005.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
    This folder contains information of the development of new antipersonnel weapons and material on non-lethal weapons.
  - Eugenics, 1959; MS005.001.005.00039 (Box 5)
    This folder contains Earle Reynold's article: "Irradiation and Human Evolution."
  - Fernald State School, 1958 -- 1994; MS005.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Fernald State School: Additional materials on Dr. Benda and residents, 1957 -- 2006; MS005.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - Fernald State School: Assorted materials and examples of relative research, 1957 -- 1994; MS005.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - Fernald State School: Dr. C. Benda, 1957 -- 1963; MS005.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
    Folder label reads: found at Dr. Clemens Benda's home sale.
  - Fernald State School: Findings of the Task Force, 1994; MS005.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - Fernald State School: materials from Children's Bureau archives, 1950 -- 1994; MS005.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - Fernald State School: Miscellaneous research, 1954 -- 2006; MS005.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - Fernald State School: The Thyroid Studies and MIT testimony, 1994; MS005.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
    This folder contains "The Thyroid Studies: A follow-up report on the use of radioactive materials in human subject research that involved residents of state-operated facilities within the Commonwealth of Massachusetts from 1943 through 1973," and J. David Litster's testimony on MIT nutrition research involving radioactive tracers and human subjects.
  - Films, exhibits and plays; Veterans and radiation survivors, 1946 -- 1999; MS005.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - GAO Senate report: Nuclear Health and Safety, 1992; MS005.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
    This folder contains GAO/RCED-92-182 "Nuclear Health and Safety: Mortality Study of Nuclear Test Participants is Flawed."
  - GAO Senate report: Operation Crossroads, 1985; MS005.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
    This folder contains GAO/RCED-86-15 "Operation Crossroads: Personnel Radiation Exposure Estimates Should Be Improved."
  - Genetics, 1954 -- 1986; MS005.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - German research: World War II aviation medicine, 1942 -- 1968; MS005.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - German research: World War II Nazi doctors and scientists, 1950 -- 2000; MS005.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - German research: World War II relating to radiation, 1948 -- 1950; MS005.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - German research: World War II reference, 1978 -- 1979; MS005.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Government documents, misc., 1951 -- 2002; MS005.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Government test reviews, legal acts and test victims, 1956 -- 1986; MS005.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Great Britain - Nuclear test information, 1950 -- 2001; MS005.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Health and Energy Institute: Directory of Radiation Victims Organizations, 1984; MS005.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Human experimentation: US government sponsored experiments, 1956 -- 1975; MS005.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Human Radiation Experiments Associated with the U.S. Department of Energy and Its Predecessors, 1995; MS005.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
    Report DOE/EH-0491.
  - Human Radiation Experiments: The Department of Energy Roadmap to the Story and the Records, 1995; MS005.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
    Report DOE/EH-0445.
  - Human Radiation Experiments: Stakeholder Workshop, Part I Transcripts, 1996; MS005.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Human Radiation Experiments: Stakeholder Workshop, Part II Brochures, Notes, Handouts, 1996; MS005.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Human Radiation Interagency Working Group, 1997; MS005.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
    This is the report DOE/EH-0542, "Building Public Trust: Actions to respond to the report of the Advisory Committee on Human Radiation Experiments."
  - Human Rights activists, correspondence, 1978 -- 1998; MS005.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Human testing: newspaper articles and clippings, 1981 -- 1997; MS005.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Japan: Correspondence and ephemera, 1964 -- 1987; MS005.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
    This folder contains letters sent to Marlowe by Veterans and family members of Veterans who were present for the occupation of Hiroshima and Nagasaki. This folder also contains a photographic print of Al and Jacqui Maxwell from an exhibit by photographer, James Lerager.
  - Japan: Correspondence from leaders, 1981 -- 1995; MS005.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
    This folder contains letters sent to Marlowe by Veterans who were present for the occupation of Hiroshima and Nagasaki.
  - Japan: Correspondence some with missing pages, 1981 -- 1985; MS005.001.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Japan: Hiroshima and Nagasaki, 1946 -- 1995; MS005.001.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Japan: Hiroshima and Nagasaki correspondence and research materials, 1983 -- 1986; MS005.001.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Japan: Hiroshima and Nagasaki correspondence, 1980 -- 1985; MS005.001.006.00034 (Box 6)
    This folder contains some correspondence from Veterans and their families, as well as materials from Bill Griffin of NAAV.
  - Japan: NAAV listing of Hiroshima and Nagasaki veterans, 1980 -- 1985; MS005.001.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - Japan: articles and reports on veteran health, 1980 -- 1994; MS005.001.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - Japan: POW ephemera and correspondence, 1976 -- 1985; MS005.001.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - Kane, Col. Nicholas, 1948 -- 1983; MS005.001.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - Katz, Jay: Informed consent, 1994; MS005.001.006.00039; Katz, Jay (Box 6)
    This folder contains the report, "Informed Consent: Must it remain a Fairy Tale?"
  - Marlow, Sandra: activist file, 1977 -- 1998; MS005.001.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - Marlow, Sandra: Box inventories, 2006; MS005.001.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - Marlow, Sandra: Congressional correspondence, 1978 -- 2000; MS005.001.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - Marlow, Sandra: Nicholas Kane research, 1948 -- 1980; MS005.001.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - McGovern, Col. Daniel: Correspondence, 1948 -- 1988; MS005.001.006.00044 (Box 6)
    Correspondence regarding McGovern's film: Japan!
  - Meet Mr. Bomb: A practical guide to nuclear extinction, 1982; MS005.001.006.00045 (Box 6)
  - Microwaves: effects on CNS and behavior, 1985; MS005.001.006.00046 (Box 6)
  - Mind control: Government experiments and other research, 1940 -- 1985; MS005.001.006.00047 (Box 6)
  - NAAV activists: correspondence, 1978 -- 1987; MS005.001.006.00048 (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV).
  - NAAV: assorted newsletters, studies and reports, 1981 -- 1998; MS005.001.006.00049 (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV). This folder contains Thomas J. Houser's "Statement of the NAAV presented to the Joint Meeting of the Senate and House Veterans Affairs Committee."
  - NAAV: Atomic Veterans Newsletter, 1981 -- 1998; MS005.001.006.00050 (Box 6)
  - NAAV: Atomic Veterans Newsletter, 1984 -- 1996; MS005.001.006.00051 (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV). This folder contains an issue of the Atomic Veterans Newsletter from 1984, as well as consecutive issues from Summer 1991 to Summer/Fall 1996.
  - NAAV: Atomic Veterans Newsletter, 1996 -- 2001; MS005.001.006.00052 (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV). This folder contains an issue of the Atomic Veterans Newsletter from Winter 1996/1997 to Fall 2001.
  - NAAV: Atomic Veterans Newsletter, 2001 -- 2004; MS005.001.006.00053 (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV). This folder contains an issue of the Atomic Veterans Newsletter from 2001 to Fall 2004.
  - NAAV: Atomic Veterans Newsletter, 2004 -- 2006; MS005.001.006.00054 (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV). This folder contains an issue of the Atomic Veterans Newsletter from 2004 to Winter 2005/2006.
  - NAAV: Atomic Veterans Newsletter, 2006 -- 2012; MS005.001.006.00055 (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV). This folder contains an issue of the Atomic Veterans Newsletter from July 2004 to November 2012.
  - NAAV/CARS: correspondence, 1981 -- 1987; MS005.001.006.00056 (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV), Center for Atomic Radiation Studies (CARS).
  - NAAV: Co-medical Coordinator Jess Clark correspondence, 1981 -- 1984; MS005.001.006.00057a (Box 6)
  - NAAV: Leader correspondence, 1982 -- 1986; MS005.001.006.00057b (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV). This folder contains many letters from Bill Griffin regarding Japan.
  - NAAV/NARS: correspondence, 1982 -- 1986; MS005.001.006.00058 (Box 6)
    National Association of Atomic Veterans (NAAV), National Association of Radiation Survivors (NARS).
  - NAAV/NARS: Sandra Marlow correspondence, 1984 -- 1998; MS005.001.006.00059 (Box 6)
  - NAAV/NARS: articles by advocates Carl Johnson and Bianca Murphy, 1962 -- 1990; MS005.001.006.00060; Johnson, Carl J.; Murphy, Bianca Cody (Box 6)
  - NAAV/NARS: member correspondence, 1982 -- 2005; MS005.001.006.00061; Johnson, Carl J.; Murphy, Bianca Cody (Box 6)
  - NAAV/NARS: scientist advocates, 1981 -- 1983; MS005.001.006.00062; Johnson, Carl J.; Murphy, Bianca Cody (Box 6)
  - National Archives microfilm publication M1109, 1982; MS005.001.007.00001; National Archives and Records Administration (Box 7)
    This folder contains the pamphlet: "Correspondence ("Top Secret") of the Manhattan Engineer District, 1942-1946."
  - National Archives: Partial FOIA request of fire in St. Louis, 1973; MS005.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - National Archives: St. Louis record center fire FOIA request, 1973; MS005.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - National Bureau of Standards: Maximum permissible radiation exposures to man, 1958; MS005.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
    This is an addendum to National Bureau of Standards Hanbook 59, "Permissible Does from External Sources of Ionizing Radiation."
  - NARS/CARS: Quick scan list and information, 1984 -- 1995; MS005.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - NARS: Directives and correspondence [1 of 2], 1984 -- 1989; MS005.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
    NARS (National Association of Radiation Survivors).
  - NARS: Directives and correspondence [2 of 2], 1980 -- 1987; MS005.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - NARS: Newsletters, 1992 -- 2005; MS005.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - NCRV: Invisible Violence - Proceedings of the National Citizens Hearings for Radiation Victims, 1980; MS005.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
    NCRV (National Committee for Radiation Victims).
  - National Research Council: government archival material, 1974 -- 1992; MS005.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Network News, 1983; MS005.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
    This folder contains Network News (Jan/Feb 1983), the newsletter for the National Women's Health Network.
  - Nevada, Desert Rock: correspondence, 1981 -- 1988; MS005.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Nevada, Desert Rock: correspondence, 1955 -- 1983; MS005.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Nevada, Desert Rock: Nuclear test, correspondence, 1980 -- 1983; MS005.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Nevada list: Government records and studies, 1951 -- 1981; MS005.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Nevada: Western Shoshone territory, legal reports and newsletter, 1997 -- 2002; MS005.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - Nevada: Western Shoshone territory, legal reports and newsletter, 1997 -- 2002; MS005.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - North Carolina radioactive waste dump, related newsletters, 1995 -- 1996; MS005.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - Nuclear tests: Personnel Review Program, history, 1986; MS005.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
    This folder contains, "For the record - A history of the nuclear test personnel review program, 1978-1986" prepared by the Defense Nuclear Agency (DNA).
  - Nuclear tests: Related events, exhibits, conferences and brochures, 1953 -- 1990; MS005.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Nuclear War: A public health concern, 1983; MS005.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
    A publication of the Massachusetts Department of Public Health.
  - Nuclear weapons' effect on humans: reference materials, 1972 -- 1986; MS005.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Nuclear testing: newspaper and magazine articles, 1947 -- 2001; MS005.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
    This folder includes a portion of the Pulitzer Prize winning book, "Plutonium Files."
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory: A citizen's guide to Oak Ridge, 1992; MS005.001.007.00024 (Box 7)
    Published by the Oak Ridge Education Project and The Foundation for Global Sustainability.
  - Pacific Atomic and Hydrogen bomb tests, correspondence, 1979 -- 1984; MS005.001.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Pacific Atomic and Hydrogen bomb tests, correspondence, 1980 -- 1981; MS005.001.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Pacific tests: Test veterans, 1975 -- 1982; MS005.001.007.00027a (Box 7)
    This folder contains information on veteran, Don Baker, and includes portions of his medical records.
  - Pacific tests: Operation Crossroads, correspondence [1], 1979 -- 1986; MS005.001.007.00027b (Box 7)
  - Pacific tests: Operation Crossroads, correspondence [2], 1946 -- 1982; MS005.001.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Pacific tests: Operation Crossroads, correspondence [3], 1946 -- 1986; MS005.001.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Pacific tests: Operation Crossroads, reports, 1983 -- 1986; MS005.001.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Pacific tests: Operation Crossroads- The official pictorial record, 1946; MS005.001.007.00031 (Box 7)
    Produced by the U.S. Office of the Historian and Joint Task Force One.
  - Pacific tests: Eniwetok Atoll, 1954 -- 1981; MS005.001.007.00032 (Box 7)
    This folder contains correspondence, certificates of participation and clinical reports.
  - Pacific tests: Operation Crossroads government research, 1946 -- 1986; MS005.001.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Pacific tests: Operation Crossroads, 1946 -- 1965; MS005.001.007.00034 (Box 7)
    This folder contains USS Haven and Test Baker safety reports.
  - Pacific tests: US Naval Station, Kwajalien telephone directory, 1954; MS005.001.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Pilgrim Nuclear Power Station, 1986; MS005.001.007.00036 (Box 7)
    This folder contains the publication, "Emergency Public Information - What to do in case of an emergency at Pilgrim Nuclear Power Station..."
  - Psychological research (some in Massachusetts), 1948 -- 1960; MS005.001.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Radiation: Government research on effects, 1956 -- 1982; MS005.001.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Radiation health effects: History, articles, reports, 1955 -- 1997; MS005.001.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - Radiation levels: reports and articles, 1946 -- 1965; MS005.001.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Radiation: Newspaper and magazine articles, 1995 -- 2001; MS005.001.007.00041 (Box 7)
  - Radiation: Health journal articles, 1984 -- 1993; MS005.001.007.00042 (Box 7)
  - Radiation tests and experiments, 1981 -- 1994; MS005.001.007.00043 (Box 7)
    This folder includes information on the cannon tests in Michigan and "Project Crested Ice" in Greenland.
  - Radiation and toxicology: Reference, 1950 -- 1997; MS005.001.007.00044 (Box 7)
  - Radiation and toxicology: Reference, 1972 -- 1987; MS005.001.007.00045 (Box 7)
  - Reference: Title pages, 1951 -- 1985; MS005.001.007.00046 (Box 7)
  - Reference manuals, 1985; MS005.001.007.00047 (Box 7)
    This folder contains the Defense Nuclear Agency's Reference Manual: "Background materials for the CONUS volumes."
  - Reference: radiation exposure, 1981 -- 1986; MS005.001.007.00048 (Box 7)
  - Reference: Test places and dates, 1958 -- 1998; MS005.001.007.00049 (Box 7)
  - Schmidt, Dr. Ulf: Medical ethics, 1997; MS005.001.007.00050 (Box 7)
  - Sternglass, Ernest: Articles, 1986 -- 1994; MS005.001.007.00051; Sternglass, Ernest (Box 7)
  - Task Force on Radiation and Human Rights: Human Stakeholders packet, 1997; MS005.001.007.00052 (Box 7)
  - Task Force on Radiation and Human Rights: Correspondence, 1996 -- 1997; MS005.001.007.00053 (Box 7)
  - Task Force on Radiation and Human Rights, notices, etc., 1994 -- 1995; MS005.001.007.00054 (Box 7)
  - Task Force on Radiation and Human Rights, stakeholders rights, 1996 -- 2001; MS005.001.007.00055 (Box 7)
  - Task Force on Radiation Victims and Veterans, 1983 -- 1985; MS005.001.007.00056a (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Lauriston: Papers from Countway Library, 1954 -- 1981; MS005.001.007.00056b (Box 7)
  - Toxicology Information Response Center, 1973; MS005.001.007.00057 (Box 7)
  - Tri-Valley CARE, 2000 -- 2002; MS005.001.007.00058 (Box 7)
    This folder contains articles and newsletters about the Livermore National Laboratory.
  - Tri-Valley CARE: Nuclear con-fusion, 1998; MS005.001.007.00059 (Box 7)
    This folder contains the publication, Nuclear Con-Fusion - The National Ignition Facility: Flawed rationale, hight cost, and security risks.
  - Veterans: correspondence, 1980 -- 1999; MS005.001.007.00060 (Box 7)
  - Veterans: correspondence with no name or missing pages, 1975 -- 1995; MS005.001.007.00061 (Box 7)
  - Veterans Administration: Articles on Atomic Veterans, 1974 -- 2006; MS005.001.007.00062 (Box 7)
  - Weisgall, Jonathan: US Senate testimony, 1998; MS005.001.007.00063 (Box 7)
    This folder also contains the US Senate testimony of Rosalie Bertell.
  - Warren, Shields, 1948 -- 1970; MS005.001.007.00064 (Box 7)
  - Warren, Colonel Stafford, 1946 -- 1965; MS005.001.007.00065 (Box 7)
  - Warren, Colonel Stafford: UCLA files, 1946 -- 1953; MS005.001.007.00066 (Box 7)
  - Atomic Tests In Nevada, 1957-03; MS005.001.010.00001 (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
    monographs
  - Family Fallout Shelter, 1959; MS005.001.010.00002; Office of Civil and Defense Mobilization (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
  - First Global Radiation Victims Conference, 1987; MS005.001.010.00003 (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
    brochures
  - The Human Factor, Radiation and Nuclear weapons testing: A historical and personal review, 1985 -- 1995; MS005.001.010.00004; Nuclear Age History and Humanities Center (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
  - Human Radiation Experiments 1946-1974: The Clinton Administration's effort to find the facts, 1992 -- 2000; MS005.001.010.00005 (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
  - Nagasaki 1945, 1981; MS005.001.010.00006; Akizuki, Tatsuichirō, 1916-2005 (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
  - National Citizens' Hearing for Radiation Victims, 1980; MS005.001.010.00007 (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
  - Nuclear Warships and Naval Nuclear Weapons: A Complete Inventory, 1988-05; MS005.001.010.00008 (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
    reports
  - Operations Crossroads Bikini, Marshall Island Atomic Bomb Tests 1946, 1980; MS005.001.010.00009 (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
    publication
  - Operation Crossroads: The Official Pictorial Record, 1946; MS005.001.010.00010 (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
  - The People of Three Mile Island, 1980; MS005.001.010.00011 (Volume MS005 Shared 1)
    Inscription on title page reads: "For Sandra from Bob - Radiation Victims' Roundtable Washington DC 17 Mar 84 - let art & atoms be combined!"